Errors of the Human Body is a science fiction,
thriller, drama film directed by Eron Sheean.
Canadian scientist, Dr Geoff Burton takes up a position at a new institute in wintry Dresden in order to contribute to their most important project—a
human regeneration gene—that also has the potential to make something miraculous out of a personal tragedy that has haunted him for years.
Geoff, played by Michael Eklund.
Rebekkah, played by Karoline Herfurth.
Jarek, played by Tómas Lemarquis.
Samuel Mead, played by Rik Mayall.
Vlad, played by Ulrich Meinecke.
Sarah Burton, played by Caroline Gerdolle.
Errors of the Human Body is a 2012 psychological thriller
directed by Eron Sheean and starring Michael Eklund.
The tone is emotional and thought_provoking and intense.